I made it a bit on the sweet side.
Thank you, Philine.
What is that light?
There hasn't been a report
from the castle yet.
What will Prince Aqua do when
he finds out it was the Holy Prayer?
Assuming things follow the game's story...
Prince Aqua is a route
introduced in the sequel,
so that shouldn't matter.
But now that the game's practically over,
what if we're moving
on to the sequel now?
Pardon me.
I'm told that the light we saw earlier
was the result of defective
magical equipment.
And Lady Tiararose
is asked to return home
until the castle's inspection
of said equipment is complete.
I see. Understood.
So it was defective magical equipment.
I'm glad it was nothing serious.
Tiara, I'll see you home.
All right, thank you.
I'd really rather not go home.
I want to see for myself
where the game goes next.
I just hope Prince Aqua doesn't
take the heroine's hand...
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
The Sweetest Kiss in the World
Enter.
I've just returned.
That took a long time. What happened?
Well...
I was surprised to learn that Lady Akari,
the girl by Prince Hartknights's side
at the graduation party,
has learned to use the Holy Prayer.
It can't be... Lady Akari did?!
This has become rather problematic.
Lady Akari, of all people...
The Holy Prayer is
a power desired by all nations.
The benefits it brings are so great
that any nation possessing it
can enjoy total peace.
Yes, which is why those who
can use it often marry royalty.
Every royal family wants
to make it their own.
Indeed.
It's likely that Lapis Lazuli will make
that girl marry Prince Hartknights
so that they won't ever lose her.
Probably so.
But we can at least use the power
of Marinforest to intervene.
If we can obtain the Holy Prayer,
our nation will prosper even more.
The girl who can use the Holy Prayer, eh?
I want her.
It's been ten days since then,
but I still know nothing
about the Holy Prayer.
Since my father is the prime minister,
I'm sure he knows...
but I can't ask him about something
the royal family is keeping quiet.
"I actually know about the Holy Prayer!"
I can't tell him that, though.
I haven't seen Prince Aqua
since that day either.
Does he not know about
the Holy Prayer yet?
Or... if he does know about it...
Lady Tiararose.
Preparations to depart
for Marinforest are complete.
You can go there whenever you're ready.
Of course, I will
accompany you all the way.
Thank you, Philine.
But when will you be departing?
Isn't it nearly time for Prince Aquasteed
to return home as well?
It is.
It's so frustrating that I can't do
anything but await word from him.
Why isn't Prince Aqua here yet?
I thought once he saw
the Holy Prayer's power,
he'd immediately say he wants me
and head here to get me.
And then I go to Marinforest
with Prince Aqua,
and then we get married!
Or that's what I expected,
but it's been two weeks!
Darn it, Prince Aqua!
Just get here already!
Philine, what do you think?
It looks absolutely delicious!
Oh, good!
Prince Aqua is coming to see me.
The details must have
finally been decided... right?
It'll be fine.
Father didn't say anything,
so I'm sure he won't bring bad news.
I hope Prince Aqua will like these.
I'm sorry I haven't been able to
come here very much of late.
The preparations
have been taking up all my time.
Please, don't worry about that.
I wonder what's wrong with Prince Aqua...
The truth is, the engagement
has been settled.
Lady Akari's, that is.
What?
Lady Akari and... whom?
It wouldn't surprise me
if he's been working
to get his hands on the Holy Prayer.
So then... it's going to happen again?
No! Please, don't take
Prince Aqua from me!
Anything but that!
Lady Akari and Prince Hartknights
are now formally engaged.
He's the man who hurt you.
I imagine you feel conflicted
about this, but...
It's not... with Prince Aqua...
Tiara?
I'm sorry. I was just so relieved.
I thought you were getting
engaged to Lady Akari.
I was so scared.
Why would you think that?
I would never choose anyone but you.
I'm sorry I made you feel so uneasy.
Come now, don't cry.
I'm not...
Huh?
Prince Aqua...
Tiara, I missed you so.
As did I.
Thank goodness.
Thank goodness Prince Aqua
didn't choose Lady Akari.
I'm taking you with me to Marinforest.
You'll stay by my side
for the rest of our lives, won't you?
Of course, Prince Aqua.
Good evening, Lady Tiara.
Lady... Akari?
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
Good evening, Lady Tiara.
Lady... Akari?
You know, I've given it a lot of thought.
Lady Tiara, you're a player
of this game, aren't you?
The Ring of Lapis Lazuli
The game...
So Lady Akari really is like me.
I mean, you're the only thing
that differs from the game.
Everything else went according
to the game's events,
but the ending didn't go right at all!
Um... I'm not sure I understand.
There's no need to play dumb!
Here I was planning to marry
Prince Hartknights and be happy...
but then along came my
favorite, Prince Aqua!
I couldn't believe it!
But Prince Aqua is
the main route in the sequel,
so I thought I'd be content with
Prince Hartknights, my second favorite...
but if I can marry Prince Aqua,
I'd obviously rather have him!
You don't even know anything
about the sequel, do you?
About the adorable
heroine in Marinforest?
What?
I knew it!
I was trying to trick you into
admitting it. I'm so glad it worked!
I reincarnated.
I remember playing
the game, but that's all.
Hmm... So that means...
you died before even playing the sequel?!
That's unbelievable!
You poor thing! There's no otome game
out there anywhere near as amazing!
Prince Hartknights is great,
but Prince Aqua in the sequel
is so, so much better!
The sequel's heroine is a duke's
daughter in Marinforest named Icilla,
and just when Prince Aqua
is feeling fed up with
the fiancée the state chose for him,
he meets her on the seashore!
The sequel's heroine?
The event CG for that scene is just gorgeous!
I lost track of how
many times I played it!
Anyway, I think you know this,
but I can use the Holy Prayer.
And if I tell my beloved Prince Aqua
that, I'll be able to marry him.
So please break up with him.
No!
Why not?
I love him so much more than you do,
and I played the game so many times!
Prince Aqua is not a game! He's a person!
I know that, of course!
But the way you're looking at this
ignores his wishes!
What are you talking about?
As the crown prince of a major
country, once he finds out,
he'll obviously want me.
So just...
What are you...
I was thinking, what about a scenario
where Lady Tiara gets injured
and her engagement is called off?
Don't worry. It'll only make you
fall asleep a little.
You can relax.
You know you'll never get away with this!
Well, I'm the heroine,
so when it's all well and truly over,
I'm getting the happy ending!
Come forth, thunder!
Thank goodness.
Looks like I made it in time.
Prince Aqua...
Wh-Why...
is Prince Aqua here?
I'm sorry. I see I wasn't in time after all.
What is going on here?!
Lady Akari, you will
explain this, won't you?
It's not what you think, Prince Aqua!
I've learned how to use the Holy Prayer!
But it looks like I'll be forced
to marry Prince Hartknights...
Please save me, Prince Aqua!
Take me with you to your kingdom!
What gives you the right?
You love Prince Hartknights, do you not?
Stay out of this, Marquis Clamentile!
Prince Aqua, won't having me
and my Holy Prayer
make your kingdom even more prosperous?
No! Please don't...
Not Prince Aqua! Please!
I know that.
I know you are in possession
of the Holy Prayer.
Then why didn't you make me your fiancée?
Don't underestimate me.
I can lead my kingdom to prosperity
even without your power.
So I don't need you.
The only one I want...
is Tiara.
Prince Aqua...
Lies...
All lies!
There's no way you wouldn't choose me...
Apprehend her.
I'm glad you're all right.
Do you have any other injuries?
No. I'm safe because
you came to my rescue.
And this thing on my cheek
is just a scratch.
Um...
Just stay like that.
After what you've been through,
you're welcome to be
a little more demanding.
Prince Aqua, thank you so much
for coming to save me.
Why do I...
have to live in a place like this?!
I was spared from more serious punishment
thanks to Lady Tiara, but still...
Come, water!
As long as I'm in here, this is
about the strongest magic I can use.
If this were an otome game,
a prince would come to save me...
Wait, this is an otome game!
Yes?
Prince Hartknights!
You came for me!
I'll prepare tea right away!
I won't be staying that long.
You don't have to.
I want to do it.
It's so boring here, I can't stand it.
You and I will be married.
Okay, understood.
You accepted that rather easily.
I heard that you...
had feelings for Prince Aquasteed.
Of course, Prince Aqua is my favorite,
but Prince Hartknights is mistaken.
I love you, too, Prince Hartknights.
Call me impudent,
but I love everything
about this otome game world!
I love you a lot!
Really?
I'll go home now.
Bring that luggage over here.
Prince Aquasteed, please
take care of our daughter.
I will, of course,
and I will make her happy.
I'm already so happy, after all.
Prince Aqua, I'm already
very happy, as well.
Well, you got me.
Preparations to depart are complete.
You're going already? We'll miss you.
After I complete
a year of bridal training,
I'll return here briefly
for my debutante party.
You can look forward to
lots of gifts from Marinforest.
I can't wait.
Be well, Tiara.
Don't do anything too reckless.
I won't.
Take care of yourselves, as well.
You, too, Philine. Be well.
Thank you. I will support
Lady Tiararose to the end.
My heart is pounding
in a way it never has before.
We're off!
There are fairies in
Marinforest, aren't there?
Yes. I'm sure they'll
give you their blessing.
I can't wait to meet them.
I was too embarrassed to do it before,
but I want to try demanding his attention.
Tiara...
Never mind!
This is as much as I can take!
Oh, Tiara, you really are just too cute.
Huh?
A letter?
It's to you, from Lady Akari.
From Lady Akari?
It's too suspicious.
I'm sorry, but I'll check it first.
Dear Lady Tiara,
This letter is the strongest magic
I'm able to use in the white tower.
I'm going to do my best to be happy
with Prince Hartknights,
so please find your happiness, too.
I feel this is a bit
too convenient, but...
If you lose to the sequel's heroine,
I'll never forgive you!!
Is this... Japanese?
If you lose to the sequel's heroine,
I'll never forgive you!!
I'll never forgive you!
Prince Aqua, may I keep this letter?
Well, I don't mind...
If I ever feel discouraged,
I'll look at this to cheer up.
I won't lose to the sequel heroine
I haven't even met yet!
The crown prince has returned.
Now, I wonder what sort of girl
he's brought home.
The Mermaid Knows Not of Love
I'm so happy I get to see the ocean
with Prince Aqua!
Who's that smiling on the beach?
Could it be... the sequel's heroine?!